<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Serious Project</string>
    <string name="category_one">Category 1</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn more</string>
    <string name="category_two">Category 2</string>
    <string name="category_three">Category 3</string>
    <string name="serious_company">Serious company</string>
    <string name="main_page">Main page</string>
    <string name="open_menu">Open menu</string>
    <string name="plays_and_blows">Plays and blows</string>
    <string name="vga">VGA cable</string>
    <string name="vga_desc">Connects electronic devices to transmit video signals</string>
    <string name="usb">Double usb</string>
    <string name="usb_desc">Allows direct charging of one or two USB-compatible electronic devices</string>
    <string name="laptop_battery">Laptop battery</string>
    <string name="laptop_battery_desc">Provides power for a laptop, allowing portable use without the need to connect to an electrical outlet.</string>
    <string name="audio_wave_adapter">Sound wave - audio jack adapter</string>
    <string name="audio_wave_adapter_desc">Allows the conversion of sound wave signals to signals compatible with an audio jack, enabling connection to various audio devices.</string>
    <string name="radio_alarm">Alarm clock radio with big button</string>
    <string name="radio_alarm_desc">Combines the functions of an alarm clock and a radio, equipped with a large, easy-to-press button, perfect for quickly turning off the alarm.</string>
    <string name="usb_cover">Peripheral link cap</string>
    <string name="usb_cover_desc">Protects the USB port from dust, dirt, and damage, ensuring a longer device lifespan.</string>
    <string name="thermal_paste_spatula">Putty for applying thermal conductive paste</string>
    <string name="thermal_paste_spatula_desc">Allows precise and even application of thermal paste on electronic components, ensuring effective cooling.</string>
    <string name="wired_headphones">Tape-reinforced headphones</string>
    <string name="wired_headphones_desc">Provide high-quality sound and comfortable use, ideal for listening to music, watching movies, and gaming.</string>
    <string name="stylus">Macbook stylus</string>
    <string name="stylus_desc">Enables precise navigation and drawing on touch screens, perfect for use on tablets and smartphones.</string>
    <string name="radio_pcie_adapter">Adapter electromagnetic waves - PCIE</string>
    <string name="radio_pcie_adapter_desc">Converts radio wave signals to be compatible with the PCIE port, enabling wireless connectivity with a computer.</string>
    <string name="console_controller">Windows XP console controller</string>
    <string name="console_controller_desc">Allows game control on consoles compatible with Windows XP, providing comfortable and intuitive gameplay.</string>
    <string name="scanner">USB-compatible scanner</string>
    <string name="scanner_desc">Converts documents and images into digital format, allowing for easy archiving and sharing of files.</string>
    <string name="usb_b_cable">USB-B cable</string>
    <string name="usb_b_cable_desc">Used for connecting peripheral devices, such as printers, to computers, providing a stable connection and fast data transfer.</string>
    <string name="universal_cable_x">Universal cable X</string>
    <string name="universal_cable_x_desc">A versatile cable that allows the connection of various electronic devices, providing fast data transfer and a stable connection.</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add to cart</string>
    <string name="product_desc">Product description</string>
    <string name="serious_comp_desc">We are a serious company. Our company is serious.</string>
    <string name="quality">Quality</string>
    <string name="trust">Trust</string>
    <string name="guarantee">Guarantee</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="peripherals">Peripherals</string>
    <string name="cables">Cables</string>
    <string name="gadgets">gadgets</string>
    <string name="offer_otd">Offer of the day</string>
    <string name="more_info">More information about product</string>
    <string name="laptop_battery_det">A laptop battery is an essential component that allows portable use of the device without the need to connect it to an electrical outlet. It provides long-lasting and stable performance for the laptop thanks to its high capacity and high-quality cells. It is compatible with various laptop models, making it a versatile solution. With built-in protections, it safeguards the device against overcharging, overheating, and short circuits. The battery replacement process is simple and quick, allowing for immediate restoration of full laptop functionality. It is perfect for individuals who need reliable power daily and on the go.</string>
    <string name="audio_wave_adapter_det">The sound wave adapter - audio jack allows the conversion of sound wave signals to signals compatible with an audio jack. It is an essential accessory for individuals who want to connect their audio devices to various sound sources. The adapter is easy to use and compatible with a wide range of devices, such as smartphones, computers, and stereo systems. Its compact size makes it convenient to carry and store. Made from high-quality materials, it ensures long-lasting use without loss of sound quality. Its design guarantees a stable connection without interference. The adapter also features a built-in noise filter, which improves sound quality. The installation and removal of the adapter are quick and hassle-free. It is perfect for individuals who frequently travel and need a reliable solution for connecting their audio devices. It allows you to enjoy your favorite music anywhere, anytime.</string>
</resources>